Narrator: 1
A1: Hi, Kim. Do you want to come to the theater with me this Saturday?
B1: Saturday? I can’t – it’s my brother’s 21st birthday!
We’re having a big party at my parents’ house.
A1: Oh, that sounds great!
Have a wonderful time – and say "happy birthday" from me!
Narrator: 2
A2: Are you in the office next week?
B2: No, I’m on vacation.
A2: Where are you going?
B2: Australia!
A2: Lucky you!
When do you get back?
B2: On the 30th.
A2: Wow! That’s a long vacation.
B2: Yeah, three weeks!
I can’t wait.
Narrator: 3
A3: You drink a lot of coffee!
B3: Yes, this is my fifth this morning.
A3: It’s not good for you, you know.
B3: I know, but I can’t wake up without it.
Narrator: 4
A4: Where’s the restaurant?
B4: It’s not far.
It’s on the corner of Park Avenue and 53rd.
A4: Great. See you there at 7:30.
Narrator: 5
A5: Good morning. I’m here to see Maria Diaz.
My name’s Brian Sanders.
B5: Just a moment, sir, I’ll call her…
Hi, Maria. There’s a Mr. Sanders here to see you…
OK, sir. Could you sign in here?
Great. You can go right up. She’s on the sixth floor.
The elevators are over there.
A5: Thank you.